Encounters are mysterious! But the world is even more so!
لقاءات البشر مغلّفة بالغموض، والعالم تلفّه طبقات أكثر حتّى
I'm so glad I'm with you!
!أنا مسرورٌ حقّاً لكوني معك
Summer! Ocean! Beach! Beware of water accidents!
!إنّه الصيف! المحيط! الشاطئ !حاذروا الحوادث المائيّة
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
It's so pretty...
يا لجمالها
Yeah.
أجل
And there are so few people...
وعدد الناس قليلٌ هنا
We found a nice place, thanks to Dad!
وجدنا مكاناً جميلاً بفضل أبي
Yeah, huh?
معكِ حقّ
More like thanks to him taking the wrong road...
بالأحرى لسلوكه الطريق الخطأ
That hits the spot!
!شعورٌ منعش
And then the next case I solved was...
...إذاً، القضيّة التي حلّيتُها ثانياً كانت
Miss...
...يا آنسة
Huh? Bartender, where's that girl who was drinking here?
ماذا؟ أيّها الساقي، أين الآنسة التي كانت تشرب هنا؟
She left a long time ago.
غادرت منذ فترة
She did?
حقّاً ذلك؟
Dad! I knew you'd be here!
أبي! كنتُ أعرف أنّك ستكون هنا
Bartender! Another beer and two juices!
!أيّها الساقي! كأس جعّة آخر، وكأسا عصير
That's okay! We're all leaving now!
!لا داعي، سنأخذه ونغادر الآن
What? I haven't had enough to drink yet.
لمَ؟ لم أشرب كفايتي بعد
What're you talking about?! It's past 10:00 already!
!ما الذي تتكلّم عنه؟ تجاوزت الساعة العاشرة
Wouldn't it be lame for the great Mori Kogoro
أيّها العمّ، لن يليق بالعظيم موري كوغورو
to get wasted in a place like this?
أن يثمل في مكانٍ كهذا، أليس كذلك؟
Yeah, that is true.
أجل، معك حقّ
He's so easy to manipulate.
يسهل التلاعب به
Umm, are you the famous detective, Mori Kogoro-san?
المعذرة، أأنت ذاك المتحرّي الشهير موري كوغورو-سان؟
Yes, that's right.
أجل
This is amazing!
!مذهل
Could you sit with us and tell us about your exploits?!
هلّا جلست معنا وحكيت لنا عن قضاياك التي حللتها؟
It'll be our treat!
!سندعوك على حسابنا
Oh, that'd be great!
!شكراً
Come on, Dad!
!أبي
Quit that!
!اصمت
We were having drinks as friends here!
!كنّا نشرب كصديقين هنا
Famous detective or not, to be frank, you'd be a pest!
سواء كنتَ متحرّياً شهيراً أم لا، ستشّل إزعاجاً لا أكثر بصراحة
Hey! Tanaka!
!أنت! تاناكا
Dad, let's go.
أبي، لنرجع
Yeah...
أ-أجل
I'm sorry! He seems to be drunk!
آسف، يبدو أنّه ثمل
Creep.
شخص بغيض
Tanaka-san!
!تاناكا-سان
Have you seen Mitsuko?!
تاناكا-سان! هل رأيت ميتسوكو؟
We made plans for an hour ago,
اتّفقنا على اللقاء في محلّ
Yamada Tomoko Sekine Mitsuko's friend
يامادا توموكو صديقة سيكيني ميتسوكو المقرّبة
but she never showed up,
قبل ساعة ولم تأتي
and she's not at home!
!ليست في المنزل أيضاً
Dunno. Haven't seen her.
لا أدري، لم أرها
Besides, she and I have nothing to do with each other.
كما لا علاقة تربطني بتلك المرأة
Could you leave?
هلّا غادرتِ؟
I don't feel so good...
...أشعر بتوعّك
This is a hangover, if I ever had one...
هذا أثر ثمالة بلا شكّ
Dad!
!أبي
Over here!
!هنا
The water's nice! You should swim!
!الماء رائع! فلتأت للسباحة
I feel sick! Swim all you want!
!لا أشعر بأيّ روعة! اسبحا كما تشاءان
There you have it! So let's swim by ourselves!
سمعتَه، لنسبح بمفردنا إذاً
Okay!
أجل
Oh, yeah! I hear it gets a lot deeper really fast, so be careful!
بالمناسبة، سمعتُ أنّ قاع الماء ينحدر بسرعة أمامنا، لذا توخّ الحذر
Okay!
!حسناً
So, were you the first to find her?
إذاً، أكنتَ من وجد الجثّة؟
No, they were the ones who first found her...
كلّا، كانا من اكتشفاها
This rope...
...هذا الحبل
That hurt!
!مؤلم
Hey, you! Don't scamper around and get in the police's way!
أنت! لا تتجوّل في المكان !وتعترض عمل الشرطة
Pardon the late introduction. I'm Mori Kogoro, a private detective.
،أعتذر على التأخّر في التعريف بنفسي أنا موري كوغورو، مُتحرٍّ خاص
Mori... You mean the famous detective?!
موري... أتقصد ذاك المتحرّي الشهير؟
Yes! The fact I'm known this far away puts me at a loss for words!
أجل! لم أعلم أنّ اسمي معروف !حتّى في بلدة بعيدة كهذه
Whatever. You're not at a loss at all.
يا إلهي، لست مغلوباً البتّة
Mitsuko!
!ميتسوكو
Mitsuko?
ميتسوكو؟
You know the victim, Miss?
أتعرفين الضحيّة يا آنسة؟
Yes, she's Sekine Mitsuko. My best friend.
أجل، إنّها سيكيني ميتسوكو، صديقتي المقرّبة
I can't believe this would happen...
...لم أتصوّر أن يحصل هذا لها
Excuse me, Detective.
المعذرة سيّدي المحقّق
Sorry to keep you waiting.
وصلت
Oh, you're...
...أنت
We meet again.
التقينا مُجدداً
Oh? You know each other?
ماذا؟ أتعرفان بعضكما؟
No, we just happened to meet once.
كلا، التقينا مصادفةً مرّةً لا أكثر
Oh, I see.
هكذا إذاً
In that case, this is Dr. Tanaka. I asked him to examine the body.
في تلك الحالة، هذا الطبيب تاناكا الذي طلبتُ منه فحص الجثّة
He's the most skilled doctor in town!
!إنّه أبرع طبيب في هذه البلدة
It's a real honor.
...يا للمقام
And this is the famous detective, Mori Kogoro-san!
!وهذا المتحرّي المعروف، موري كوغورو-سان
Your reputation precedes you.
سمعتك تسبقك
If it's not too much to ask, I'd love to have your help on this case.
إذا لم تمانع، فأتمنّى مساعدتك لنا في هذه القضيّة
I have no objections.
لا أمانع إطلاقاً
That's great to hear! After all, this is a quiet little town!
!شكراً! فهذه بلدة هادئة صغيرة
We're not used to incidents like this at all!
لسنا معتادين على حوادث كهذه البتّة
Umm, shouldn't I begin my examination?
المعذرة، ألا يُفترض بي بدء الفحص؟
Oh, right! I forgot!
!صحيح! نسيت
Then I'll get started.
سأبدأ إذاً
Pardon me.
اعذريني
Well, Doctor?
إذاً حضرة الطبيب؟
Hmm... I can't say anything for sure until we get to the hospital,
حسناً... لا أستطيع قول شيءٍ حتّى نفحصها في المشفى
but this may have been a suicide.
لكن لعلّه كان انتحاراً
Suicide?!
انتحار؟
See? There are no external injuries or signs of a struggle at all.
انظر، لا توجد إصابات خارجيّة أو آثار مقاومة البتّة
If it had been a murder, there would've been a fight
لو كانت جريمة قتل، لوقع اشتباك بينما
as the killer tried to throw her into the sea.
يحاول القاتل إغراقها في المحيط
Yet, she doesn't have a single scratch on her.
مع ذلك، لا توجد عليها أيّة ندب
Oh, I see! You're absolutely right!
فهمت، فهمت، أنت محقّ تماماً
She probably rowed out to sea in a boat or something,
لعلّها جدّفت في البحر بطوف أو ما شابه
tied the rock to her feet, and drowned herself.
وربطت صخرةً بقدميها، وأغرقت نفسها
What's with this guy?
ما خطب هذا الشخص؟
He says he can't say much before going to the hospital,
يقول أنّه لا يستطيع أن يعرف ،حتّى يفحص في المشفى
but it's like he's trying to force the idea she committed suicide.
لكن كأنّه يحاول فرض فكرة الانتحار
Though, that's only my guess for now.
رغم أنّ ذلك يبقى تخميني لا أكثر
Now, if you'll please take the body to the hospital...
حسناً، هلّا نقلتم الجثّة للمشفى رجاءً؟
I'll come with you.
سأرافقك في تلك الحالة
Murderer...
...قاتل
Mitsuko wouldn't commit suicide! He killed her!
!لن تقدم ميتسوكو على الانتحار! قتلها ذاك الشخص
Are you saying that doctor is a murderer?
أتقصدين بالقاتل ذاك الطبيب؟
That's right!
!صحيح
Do you have any sort of proof?
ألديكِ دليلٌ ما؟
I have no proof! But,
...لا دليل لديّ، لكن
he and Mitsuko had been dating!
!كان ذلك الرجل يواعد ميتسوكو
But he didn't seem to act that way...
...لكن لم يبد عليه ذلك
He even promised to marry her,
،وعد بأن يتزوّجها حتّى
but then got engaged to the daughter of the head of a major hospital!
!لكنّه خطب ابنة مدير مشفى كبير
Mitsuko was in the way, so...
...لذا كانت ميتسوكو عقبةً في طريقه
Even now, he pretended not to know her!
!حتّى الآن، تظاهر بأنّه لا يعرفها
Isn't it strange he didn't even flinch after his girlfriend died?!
أليس من الغريب أنّ لا تأثّر ظهر عليه !بعد موت حبيبته التي واعدها؟
Yes, that is suspicious.
ذلك مُريب بالفعل
Exactly.
صحيح
He tried to force the idea of suicide in his examination just now,
حاول فرض فكرة الانتحار في تحليله قبل قليل
and, judging from the body's condition, it's very likely he killed her!
وبناءً على حالة الجثّة، فهناك احتمالٌ عالٍ !بأنّه كان القاتل
But, if so, why do something so daring
لكن في تلك الحالة، لمَ يقوم بشيءٍ بتلك الجرأة؟
as killing her and then examining her?
يقتلها بنفسه، ثم يفحص جثّتها؟
Very well, Miss. I, the great Mori Kogoro, will reveal his true colors
حسناً يا آنسة، سأكشف أنا، المتحرّي العظيم موري كوغورو، عن وجهه الحقيقيّ
to avenge Mitsuko-san!
!وآخذ بثأر ميتسوكو-سان
Really?! Thank you!
!حقّاً؟! من فضلك
Are you really sure you can do that, old guy?
أستستطيع فعل هذا حقّاً يا عمّ؟
Police Department
مركز الشرطة
After my examination, it appears she did drown to death.
بعد الفحص، تيقّنا بأنّها ماتت غرقاً
All other causes were ruled out.
تمّ استبعاد كلّ المسبّبات الأخرى
Her estimated time of death is just past 10:00 last night.
وقت وفاتها المقدّر هو بعد العاشرة بقليل من ليلة البارحة
Dr. Tanaka.
الطبيب تاناكا
Yes?
نعم؟
I heard something from the victim's friend on the beach...
سمعتُ شيئاً من صديقة الضحيّة على الشاطئ قبل قليل
Is it true that you and the victim, Mitsuko-san, had been dating?
أمن الصحيح أنّك كنتَ والضحيّة ميتسوكو-سان تتواعدان؟
Say what?! Is this true, Dr. Tanaka?!
ماذا؟ أهذا صحيح يا طبيب تاناكا؟
I apologize. I should've mentioned it at the very start.
أعتذر، كان عليّ ذكر الأمر في البداية
I hear you're marrying the daughter of the head of a major hospital.
سمعت أنّك ستتزوّج ابنة مدير مشفى كبير
What about it?
وما في ذلك؟
Did that not make Mitsuko-san an obstacle?
ألم تكن ميتسوكو-سان عقبةً في طريقك؟
What are you insinuating?!
!ما الذي تلمّح له؟
It just seems strange for someone with a motive
بدا غريباً لي لا أكثر أنّ شخصاً يملك دافعاً
to conduct an autopsy when it's unclear if it was a murder or suicide.
يقوم بإجراء تشريح بينما لم يتبين ما إن كانت الحادثة جريمة قتل أم انتحاراً
It was clearly a suicide!
كان انتحاراً بكلّ وضوح
No, a lack of external injuries isn't enough. There isn't even a will.
،كلا، لا يكفي عدم وجود إصابات خارجيّة ولم تكن هناك وصيّة حتّى
Could you tell us where you were at her estimated time of death?
أيمكنك إخبارنا أين كنت وما الذي كنت تفعله وقت وفاتها المقدّر؟
Last night, I was at a bar with a friend, from 8:00 to midnight.
كنت أشرب في حانة رفقة صديق البارحة من الثامنة حتّى منتصف الليل
Oh, yes. The place where I met you.
صحيح، تلك الحانة التي التقيتك فيها
What?!
ماذا؟
By car, it'd take ten minutes from that bar to the beach, one-way.
سيستغرق ذهابك من تلك الحانة للشاطئ الذي كانت عليه الجثّة 10 دقائق بالسيّارة، دون العودة
If you'd like, you can check with the owner and my friend
يمكنك مراجعة الساقي وصديقي إذا أردت
to see if I had left my seat for that long.
والتأكّد ما إن تركت مقعدي لتلك الفترة
Come to think of it, just after 10:00 was when we came to get you.
بالمناسبة، أتيت مع كونان لجلبك بعد العاشرة بقليل يا أبي
What?!
!ماذا؟
In other words, Mori-san, you can vouch for my alibi.
أي أنّ بإمكانك أن تشهد بحجّة غيابي يا موري-سان
It's a perfect alibi... Is this his source of confidence?!
إنّها حجّة غياب مطبقة... أهذا مصدر ثقته؟
But you gave the estimated time of death! I want a reexamination!
!لـ-لكنّك من أعطى وقت الوفاة المقدّر !سنحتاج لرأي شخصٍ آخر
As you like.
تفضّلوا
But you'll have to take responsibility when I'm proven innocent.
لكنك ستتحمّل المسؤولية إذا ثبتت براءتي
Alright, then!
!حسناً
Detective! Make arrangements at once!
!حضرة المحقّق، قم بالتجهيزات فوراً
Right!
حسناً
Say, Detective. This might take a long time, so can I leave?
حضرة المحقّق، قد يستغرق هذا وقتاً فهل يمكنني المغادرة؟
Oh, that would be fine.
لا أمانع ذلك
Also, can I borrow a bicycle anywhere? I want to explore this area!
أيوجد مكان حيث أستطيع استعارة درّاجة إذاً؟ أريد استكشاف المنطقة
Judging from his confident manner,
،بناءً على ثقته المفرطة
a reexamination will probably give the same results.
ستعطي إعادة التقدير النتيجة نفسها
There has to be some sort of trick! Something...
...لا بد من وجود حيلة! شيء ما
I will destroy his alibi!
...لا بدّ أن أطيح
Do you usually sit here and stare at the ocean, Mister?
أتجلس وتراقب البحر هنا عادةً يا عمّ؟
Yeah.
أجل
Yesterday, too?
وبالأمس؟
Did you notice anything unusual?
هل لاحظت أمراً غريباً؟
Nothing at all.
لا شيء
I figured...
كما ظننت
The only unusual thing is the trash that washes up every day...
الشيء الغريب الوحيد هنا هو القمامة التي تحملها الأمواج للمكان كلّ يوم
Trash?
القمامة؟
Yeah, all the trash in these waters washes up here 'cause of the tide.
أجل، كلّ قمامة هذه المياه تُحمل إلى هنا بسبب المد
Trash, huh...
...القمامة إذاً
Say, where is this trash?
أين تلك القمامة؟
I have it piled in the back.
جمعتها في الخلف
Geez! The ocean isn't a garbage dump!
!يا إلهي، المحيط ليس مكبّ قمامة
An inner tube. It's still new; is it ripped somewhere?
،إطار هوائيّ... لا يزال جديداً فهل هو ممزق في مكان؟
Is this it? There's a small hole...
هنا إذاً؟ توجد فتحة صغيرة
Hole? Small?
فتحة؟ صغيرة؟
That's it! Could it be?!
...فهمت! أيمكن
Hey, Mister!
أخبرني يا عمّ
Did this inner tube wash up today?
هل جُرف هذا الإطار الهوائيّ اليوم؟
Yeah, that's right.
أجل، صحيح
Can I have it?
أيمكنني أخذه؟
Yeah, sure.
لا مشكلة
And can I have a couple of these empty plastic bottles too?
وأيمكنني أخذ القليل من هذه القنّينات البلاستيكية الفارغة أيضاً؟
Yeah, dunno what you want with 'em, but take whatever you want.
أجل، لا أدري فيمَ ستستعملها لكن خذ ما تشاء
The flow of the tide and the deflated inner tube!
تيّار المد والإطار الهوائيّ المثقوب
If my theory is correct, these plastic bottles should make it clear!
إذا أصاب استنتاجي، فسيتوضّح كلّ شيء بهذه القنّينات البلاستيكية
Alright! Now I just wait on the beach!
حسناً، عليّ الانتظار عند الشاطئ الآن فقط
Here it comes!
!ها هي
Just as I thought! That just leaves the store that sold the inner tube!
كما ظننت! ما تبقّى هو المتجر الذي !باع ذاك الإطار الهوائيّ
The reexamination produced the same results as mine, Mori-san.
طابقتْ نتيجة إعادة التقدير نتيجتي يا موري-سان
Now, what do you have to say for yourself, Mori-san?
حسناً، كيف ستبرّر نفسك يا موري-سان؟
Is suspecting innocent people what all great detectives do?
تشتبه بأناس بريئين، أهذا ما يفعله المتحرّون العظماء؟
Oh, uhh, pardon me a minute...
حسناً، في الواقع... اعذرني قليلاً
Oh? Running away?
ماذا؟ تهرب؟
No, just the restroom. Don't wanna wet myself...
كلا، سأذهب لدورة المياه، فأنا على وشك تبليل نفسي
Damn! I was sure he did it, too...
تبّاً، كنت متأكداً أنّه كان مريباً
Alright, here we go!
!ها هي، أتت
What was that?
ما كان ذلك الصوت؟
Dad?
أبي؟
I apologize for the wait, everyone! Please come to the next room!
أعتذر على الإطالة جميعاً، تعالوا للغرفة المجاورة رجاءً
Dad!
!أبي
What is this, Mori-san?
ما الأمر يا موري-سان؟
Changing rooms to regain your bearings?
تغيّر الغرفة لإعادة ضبط موقفك؟
I suppose.
نوعاً ما
Now, then! Allow me to reveal the truth of this incident!
إذاً يا جماعة، دعوني أكشف حقيقة هذه الحادثة
This incident was a murder! And the killer was you, Dr. Tanaka!
كانت جريمة قتل! والقاتل هو أنت !أيّها الطبيب تاناكا
But, Mori-san! Wasn't it proved that Dr. Tanaka has an alibi?!
لكن يا موري-سان، ألم نتحقّق من امتلاك الطبيب تاناكا لحجّة غياب؟
Yes, he was at the bar at the victim's estimated time of death.
أجل، كان في الحانة أثناء وقت وفاة الضحيّة المقدّر
He killed her while he drank.
قتلها وهو يشرب
I-Is that possible?!
أ-أذلك ممكن؟
There's no doubt she died at the location Conan and Ran found her.
لا شكّ أنّها لقيت حتفها في المكان الذي اكتشفها كونان وران فيه
However, the actual crime took place elsewhere.
لكن وقعت الجريمة الحقيقيّة في مكانٍ مختلف
First, Tanaka-san called her to a separate location
استدعاها تاناكا-سان لمكان مختلف أوّلاً
and knocked her out with chloroform or some other drug.
وأفقدها وعيها بكلوروفورم أو وما شابه
As a doctor, obtaining such drugs would be simple.
لن يكون صعباً الحصول على تلك العقارات على طبيب مثلك
You then used rope to tie a heavy rock to her feet,
ثمّ استُخدِم حبل لربط صخرة كبيرة بقدميها
placed her in an inner tube with a small hole in it,
ووضعتها في إطار هوائيّ به ثقب صغير
and let her float in the ocean.
وتركتها تعوم في المحيط
Immediately afterward, you went to the bar with your friend...
بعد ذلك، توجّهت للحانة مع رفيقك للشراب
...to create an alibi.
لبناء حجّة غيابك
During that time, Mitsuko-san floated along the current, still alive.
أثناء ذلك، كان التيّار يتلاعب بميتسوكو-سان وهي لا تزال حيّة
There's a tidal current here that flows toward the swimming area.
يوجد تيّار مد وجزر هنا يتدفق نحو منطقة السباحة
So she was washed toward the beach while still alive.
فجُرفت للشاطئ وهي حيّة
The inner tube continued to deflate, and eventually,
...واصل الهواء التسرّب من الإطار، وبنهاية المطاف
the inner tube could no longer support her weight,
لم يعد الإطار قادراً على رفع وزنها
so Mitsuko-san sank into the sea.
فغرقت ميتسوكو-سان في البحر
All while you were drinking at the bar.
بينما كنت تشرب في الحانة
Judging from the speed at which the inner tube deflated,
،بناءً على سرعة تفرغ هواء الإطار
you likely sent her adrift at around 7:00.
فقد رميتها في البحر عند قرابة السابعة غالباً
You arrived at the bar yesterday at 8:00.
وصلت عند الحانة في الثامنة البارحة
Can you prove your alibi for 7:00?
أيمكنك إثبات حجّة غيابك للسابعة؟
Absurd! That's nothing but conjecture!
!سخافة! هذا مجرّد تخمين
She could've used the inner tube to commit suicide herself!
كان بإمكانها استعمال الإطار !الهوائيّ للانتحار أيضاً
That's not a possibility.
ذلك ليس محتملاً
What?
ماذا؟
Detective, show him a photograph of the victim's feet.
حضرة المحقّق، فلتره الصورة التي اُلتقطت لقدمَي الضحيّة
Here we are.
هذه هي
Okay, Ran.
حسناً، ران
Tie your own feet, just like in the photograph.
اربطي قدميك مثلما في الصورة
Okay.
حسناً
All done, Dad.
انتهيت يا أبي
Detective, please compare that photograph with Ran's feet.
حضرة المحقّق، قارن الصورة بقدمَي ران من فضلك
The knots are reversed.
العُقدة معكوسة
Normally, if you tie your own feet, you'll get a knot like Ran's.
في العادة، ستنتج عقدة مثل التي ربطتها ران عندما تربط قدميك بنفسك
Then why is the knot in the photograph reversed?
فلمَ العقدة في الصورة مقلوبة؟
It's because the killer tied her feet facing her.
لأنّ القاتل ربط قدميها مقابلاً لها
That doesn't mean that I killed her!
!لا يعني ذلك أنّي القاتل
Conan found a brand new inner tube with a small hole on the beach.
وجد كونان إطاراً هوائياً جديداً بثقب صغير على الشاطئ
Here it is, Detective!
ها هو حضرة المحقّق
That's the inner tube you used, isn't it?
هذا هو الإطار الذي استعملته في الجريمة، أليس كذلك؟
I-I've never seen it before!
!لـ-لم أره قبلاً
It was easy finding the shop where you bought this inner tube.
كان إيجاد المتجر الذي اشتريته منه سهلاً
After all, it is a small town.
فهي بلدة صغيرة
This is the inner tube Dr. Tanaka bought last week.
هذا هو الإطار الهوائيّ الذي اشتراه الطبيب تاناكا الأسبوع الفائت
But he said it was for an acquaintance's daughter. How strange...
لكنّه قال أنّه سيعطيه لابنة أحد معارفه، هذا غريب
The shop woman clearly remembered you buying it.
تذكّرت مالكة المحلّ شراءك له بوضوح
And you must've felt quite confident about this trick...
ولا بدّ أنّك كنت واثقاً جدّاً بهذه الحيلة
Enough not to wipe away your fingerprints from the inner tube!
بحيث لم تمح بصماتك من على الإطار
Now then, why would your fingerprints be on an inner tube
حسناً، لمَ توجد بصماتك على الإطار الذي
you said you've never seen before?
قلت أنّك لم تره قبلاً؟
Dr. Tanaka! You--?!
...طبيب تاناكا! أأنت
I wish we could've stayed another day...
ليتنا استطعنا البقاء يوماً آخر
So, Dad! I don't mind if you take the wrong road again!
إذاً يا أبي، لا نمانع إذا سلكت الطريق الخطأ مُجدداً
D-Don't be stupid! I didn't take the wrong road yesterday!
!يا-يا حمقاء! لم أخطئ في الطريق بالأمس
A case called for the great Mori Kogoro!
!بل استدعت قضيّةٌ المتحرّي العظيم موري كوغورو
I'd never take the wrong road otherwise!
وإلّا يستحيل أن أسلك الطريق الخطأ
But you got it wrong in the end anyway...
لكنّك أخطأت في النهاية
What happened, Dad?
ما الذي حصل يا أبي؟
This is the shore we just left from!
هذا الشاطئ الذي غادرناه قبل لقليل
That's strange...
...هذا غريب
I got it! The sea called us here to stay another night!
!فهمت، استدعانا البحر لنبيت ليلةً أخرى
That's stupid. Of course it didn't...
أحمق، يستحيل ذلك
But you'd never take the wrong road otherwise, right?
لكنّك قلت أنّك لن تخطئ في الطريق بخلاف ذلك، صحيح؟
Yeah! You couldn't help it; the sea called us here!
!أجل! لم يكن الأمر باليد، فالبحر استدعانا
Really?
حقّاً؟
Really!
!أجل
Yeah, huh? I'd never take the wrong road otherwise!
صحيح، وإلّا يستحيل أن أسلك الطريق الخطأ
Okay! Another night!
!حسنٌ! لنبت ليلة أخرى
He's so easy to manipulate.
يسهل التلاعب به حقّاً
What was that?
ما-ما كان ذلك؟
Kiwako-san might've been bitten by a sea snake!
!ربما عضّت أفعى بحرية كيواكو-سان
There they are! Bite marks!
!ها هي! آثار عضّ
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Scuba Diving Murder Case (Part 1)."
جريمة قتل غوص السكوبا (الجزء الأوّل)
Next Conan's hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Feather.
ريش
Don't miss it.
!ترقّبوها